

Maksim Svistukhin

DETAILS

n Prague, Czech Republic

+420 608594057

SKILLS

Excelent communication

Front-end development

Web design

Direct sales

Solution design

Team management

LANGUAGES

English

C1

Czech

C1

Russian

NATIVE

TECH SKILLS

HTML CSS JavaScript

React Git

SCSS Sketch Adobe CS

Webflow Figma

PROFILE :

First of all, I am a strong professional in communication at all levels. I have extensive experience in team management and sales, as well as excellent visualisation abilities and decent skills in SW development. Overall, I can describe myself as a person, passionate about finding solutions for rather wide range of possible issues.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Freelance Web Designer

2/2019 - Current

Prague, Czech Republic

- · Creating web applications design using the latest UI/UX trends in Figma
- · Development using a combination of Webflow, HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- · Managing and maintaining client websites

Logistics/Sales manager

12/2017 - 2/2019

Prague Group Adventures s.r.o.

Prague, Czech Republic

- Maintaining communication with service providers, tour guides and clients.
- · Recruitment and training of staff
- Managing a team of 30 employees
- · Maintaining and establishing plans for selling ancillary services to the end customer

Team-leader (Customer support) 6/2016 – 10/2017

XEROX o.s.

Prague, Czech Republic

- · Assist management with hiring procedures and training of new team members.
- · Assist with team member problems and monitor work for quality and compliance
- Communicate deadlines and goals to team members

Customer Support Advisor

11/2014 - 6/2016

XEROX o.s.

Prague, Czech Republic

- Advising customers on technical matters
- Advertising the product
- · Maintain positive relationships with customers to ensure customer loyalty

Travel agent/Coordinator

2/2014 - 12/2019

Wild East Travels

Prague, Czech Republic

- Meeting of the incoming groups
- Training of the newcomers
- · Maintaining appropriate relationships with service providers
- · Conducting sales of ancillary services

Luxury Retail Sales Manager

5/2011 - 8/2012

Boutique Vittoria

Samara, Russia

- Support sales professionals in closing sales
- Partner with sales professionals to meet their individual sales plans and KPI
- Remain current and knowledgeable of industry trends, to determine strategic opportunities to maximize sales within the market

EDUCATION

Operations management, bc

Samara State Technical University Samara, Russia

Management, bc

Czech University of Life Sciences Prague